(Penny:)-Sorry. I'll get better.
-I know you'll try.
(Leonard:)So, should we talk
about setting a date?
(Penny:)Well, I'd like to pick one that works
with my brother's schedule.
(Leonard:)Okay, and when would that be?
(Penny:)Uh, 12 to 18 months from now,
depending on good behavior.
(Amy:)-Hi, is Sheldon here?
-No, I thought he was with you.
(Amy:)He was, but he stormed off.
(Amy:)-Now he isn't answering his phone.
-What happened?
(Amy:)He was really angry
that you suggested he move out.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Amy:)I also mentioned
that he and I could live together,
(Amy:)but he was too mad at you to realize
what a great idea that is.
(Leonard:)Well, he's been having
a couple of tough days.
(Leonard:)I'm sure he's fine.
(Leonard:)He probably just needs
a little alone time to decompress.
(Amy:)You're probably right.
(Amy:)So, what are you guys doing?
(Penny:)Well, Leonard cooked for me and now
we're just having a nice dinner,
(Penny:)you know, as a newly engaged couple.
(Amy:)That's nice.